romans chapter 13 verse 11 romans
chapter 13 verse 11 the bible says and
that knowing the time that now it is
high time to awake out of sleep for now
is our salvation nearer than when we
believed the night is far spent the day
is at hand let us therefore cast off the
works of darkness and let us put on the
armor of what lights
let us not walk or let us walk honestly
as in the day not in rioting and
drunkenness not in chambering and
wantonness not in strife and envying but
put you on the Lord Jesus Christ and
make not provision for the flesh to
fulfill the lusts thereof beloved the
second way to love is to lighten up by
putting on the armor of light amen the
armor of light beloved allows us to
defeat the lusts of the flesh how many
of you remember what happened in the
book of Acts chapter two what happened
in Acts chapter two come on church what
happened in Acts chapter two the
outpouring of the holy spirit were the
disciples lightened up absolutely they
were enlightened up because the glory
the Spirit of God fell on them and the
Bible tells us in Galatians chapter five
and verse six that we are to walk in the
I'm sorry not verse six verse sixteen
Galatians chapter five verse 16 this I
say then walk in the wot spirit and you
shall not fulfill the lust of the flesh
beloved if you walk in the spirit you
are going to walk lightened up in fact
in fact the book of Psalm 37 verse 6
notice what it says here
he shall bring forth thy righteousness
as the lot as the what as the light and
thy judgment as the noonday when the
Spirit of God is dwelling in you you
know how to lighten up
you know how to walk in light and people
will see you and and notice that there
is something different about you in
other words you know how to lighten up
because the Spirit of God is dwelling in
you